luxor.com 2019-05-04

# Privacy Policy - MGM Resorts

MGM Resorts International

MGM Resorts International values your patronage and respects your privacy. This Privacy Policy ("Policy") describes the information collection, use, protection, and sharing practices of MGM Resorts International and MGM Resorts International web sites, mobile applications, electronic communications, and properties described below. If you have any questions or concerns about this Policy, please contact us at [privacy@mgmresorts.com](mailto:privacy@mgmresorts.com).

This Policy applies only to MGM Resorts International (collectively, "us," "we," or "our"), MGM Resorts International websites ("websites"), mobile applications, social media pages, and other electronic communications that we control and that post this Policy (collectively, "MGM Online Services"), and the following resorts, casinos and properties (collectively, "MGM Resorts"):

ARIA Resort and Casino (including Sky Suites) in Las Vegas, Nevada  
Beau Rivage in Biloxi, Mississippi  
Bellagio in Las Vegas, Nevada  
Borgata Hotel Casino & Spa in Atlantic City, New Jersey  
Circus Circus in Las Vegas, Nevada  
Delano in Las Vegas, Nevada  
Excalibur in Las Vegas, Nevada  
Gold Strike Resort in Tunica, Mississippi  
Las Vegas Festival Grounds in Las Vegas, Nevada  
Luxor in Las Vegas, Nevada  
Mandalay Bay in Las Vegas, Nevada  
Mandalay Bay Events Center in Las Vegas, Nevada  
Mandalay Place in Las Vegas, Nevada  
MGM Grand (including Skylofts) in Las Vegas, Nevada  
MGM Grand Detroit in Detroit, Michigan  
MGM Grand Garden Arena in Las Vegas, Nevada  
MGM National Harbor in Oxon Hill, Maryland  
MGM Northfield Park in Northfield, Ohio  
MGM Springfield in Springfield, Massachusetts  
New York-New York in Las Vegas, Nevada  
NoMad Las Vegas in Las Vegas, Nevada  
Park MGM in Las Vegas, Nevada  
Park Theater in Las Vegas, Nevada  
The Mirage in Las Vegas, Nevada  
The Park District in Las Vegas, Nevada  
The Signature at MGM Grand in Las Vegas, Nevada  
T-Mobile Arena in Las Vegas, Nevada  
Vdara Hotel & Spa in Las Vegas, Nevada  

MGM Resorts International is a corporation subject to the laws of the United States. This Policy describes our information collection, use, protection, and sharing practices in the United States. The United States may not offer a level of privacy protection as great as that offered in other jurisdictions. In jurisdictions outside of the United States where we are subject to different or more restrictive local laws, we may adjust our practices in those jurisdictions to comply with local laws. Otherwise, we make no representation that the practices described in this Policy are compliant with laws outside of the United States that apply to the collection, security, use and disclosure of information. Information that is collected or stored in jurisdictions outside of the United States may, subject to applicable law, be disclosed or transferred to the United States or other locations. When information is transferred to the United States, it will be handled in accordance with the laws of the United States.

1\. INFORMATION WE COLLECT

**Contact and other Personal Information.** When you visit, use and/or access MGM Resorts or MGM Online Services, you might provide us with, (and/or we may collect) contact and other Personal Information such as your name, date of birth, postal address, e-mail address, and telephone number, and videos, recordings, and images of you.  We may also obtain such information from third parties.

**Employment Application Information.** If you apply for a job with us, we might ask for certain information about you including, for example, your work and education history, and your profile/résumé.

**Vehicle Information.** When you park at MGM Resorts we may collect information about the vehicle you park including an image of the vehicle, the vehicle's make, model, and license plate number.  For example, we collect license plate information through technology known as “Automatic License Plate Recognition” (which captures the images of a vehicle license plates and related information such as time/date of image capture) for various safety, security and fraud prevention purposes, among others.

**Purchase and Transaction Information.** When you visit, use and/or access MGM Resorts or MGM Online Services, we might collect information about your purchases, reservations, and gaming activity (in jurisdictions where gaming is permitted).

**Sensitive Information.** When you make a purchase, visit, use and/or access MGM Resorts or MGM Online Services, or engage in other transactions or activities, you might provide us with your credit or debit card number, financial account number, biometrics, driver’s license number, government-issued identification card number, social security number, passport number, or naturalization number (“Sensitive Information”).

**Wi-Fi and Location Information.** When you use Wi-Fi services we make available at MGM Resorts, we might collect information (directly or through third parties) about the websites you visit, the type of device and browser you are using, your device identification number, your precise physical location, bandwidth used, session time, etc.  Even if you choose not to use Wi-Fi services we make available at MGM Resorts, we may still collect information concerning the precise physical location of your mobile device within and around MGM Resorts for non-marketing purposes.  With notice or your consent (and regardless of whether you use Wi-Fi service we make available at MGM Resorts), we might also collect information about the precise physical location of your mobile device within and around MGM Resorts for marketing purposes.

**Device and Browser Information.** When you visit, use, and/or access MGM Online Services, we might collect information about the type of device and browser you are using, the unique number assigned to your server or Internet connection, your physical location, and your interactions with MGM Online Services. We may also use “cookies” and similar technologies to help us recognize and serve you better. Cookies are small files that contain information sent by a web site that is saved on your computer’s hard drive. Cookies enable us to gather data such as web pages visited, links clicked, and material downloaded. Cookies also are used to put a unique identifier on your computer. This helps us to generate statistics regarding usage of MGM Online Services. There are different types of cookies including “browser” cookies (also known as “html cookies”) and Flash cookies (also known as “Local Shared Objects”). You can configure your browser to reject browser cookies or to notify you when browser cookies are offered so that you can accept or reject such cookies. However, if you reject browser cookies you may not be able to conduct some transactions or use some services on MGM Online Services. In addition, blocking or deleting browser cookies may not block or delete other types of cookies including Flash cookies.

**Social Media Information.** When you use integrated social media features on MGM Online Services, or other social media websites or mobile applications, we may obtain information such as your name and e-mail address, and videos, recordings, and images of you.

**Other Information.** We may obtain information about you from third parties, including entities that direct you to, are located at, or are accessible via, MGM Online Services or MGM Resorts, business partners, family members, and friends.

2\. INFORMATION COLLECTED BY THIRD PARTIES

**Interest-Based Advertising.**  Third parties may use cookies and similar technologies to collect information at, or through, MGM Online Services and other websites for a variety of purposes including providing you with advertisements. This type of ad-customization is sometimes referred to as “interest-based advertising.”  For more information about interest-based advertising please click [here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/faqs.asp). Please note that the use of cookies, web beacons, and similar technologies by third parties at, or through, MGM Online Services is subject to their own privacy policies, not our privacy policy. If you would like more information about your choices concerning interest-based advertising, including how you may opt-out of some uses of information collected by members of the Network Advertising Initiative and the Digital Advertising Alliance that may collect information at, or through, the MGM Online Services please click [here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).  At this time, we do not recognize automated browser signals regarding tracking mechanisms, which may include “do not track” instructions.

**Cross-Device Information.   **We participate in the Adobe Marketing Cloud Device Co-op to better understand how you use MGM Online Services across the various devices you use and to deliver tailored promotions. To learn more about how Adobe does this and to manage your choices relating to this linking of devices please click [here](https://cross-device-privacy.adobe.com/).

3\. HOW WE USE THE INFORMATION WE COLLECT

**A. Use by MGM Resorts International**

**Marketing Purposes.** We may use the information we collect for our own marketing purposes including, but not limited to: notifying you of special promotions, offers, and events via e-mail, direct mail, social media, telephone, text message, push notifications, and other means.

**Non-Marketing Purposes.** We may use the information we collect for non-marketing purposes including, but not limited to, (1) validating your identity; (2) recording gaming-related activity (in jurisdictions where gaming is permitted); (3) conducting statistical or demographic analysis; (4) processing, fulfilling, and tracking reservations, purchases, or other transactions; (5) complying with legal and regulatory requirements; (6) customizing your experience while visiting, using and/or accessing MGM Online Services; (7) protecting and defending MGM Resorts International and its affiliates against legal actions or claims; (8) preventing fraud; (9) collecting debt; (10) satisfying contractual obligations; (11) evaluating your employment application; and (12) cooperating with law enforcement or other government agencies for purposes of national security, public safety, or matters of public importance when we believe that disclosure of information is necessary or appropriate to protect the public interest (collectively “Non-Marketing Purposes”).

When it is possible to do so, we may link Personal Information such as your name or e-mail address with non-Personal Information such as the unique identifier associated with your computer or mobile device. We may also link Personal Information with other generally or publicly available information to help us identify your preferences or interests. The information we collect may also be merged with information available from other sources such as (1) companies that match e-mail addresses with postal addresses and other information; (2) credit card verification and credit services; and (3) other subsidiaries, resorts, casinos, or properties that are owned, operated, or affiliated with MGM Resorts International (individually, a “MGM Subsidiary” and collectively “MGM Subsidiaries”).

**B. Sharing within MGM Resorts International and with Subsidiaries**

We may share the information we collect for any purpose among MGM Resorts International and any individual MGM Resort, MGM Subsidiary, or MGM Online Service. However, Sensitive Information will only be shared for Non-Marketing Purposes.

**C. Sharing with Business Partners and Other Third Parties**

We may share the information we collect with our business partners and other third parties for (1) Non-Marketing Purposes, (2) joint marketing purposes, and (3) our business partners’ or our own marketing purposes. Sensitive Information will only be shared for Non-Marketing Purposes. When we provide Sensitive Information or other Personal Information to our business partners and other third parties, we require them to exercise reasonable care to protect such information and restrict the use of such information to the purposes for which it was provided to them.

**D. Certain Business Transactions**

We may share any or all of the information we collect (including Sensitive Information) with any successor to all or part of our business in connection with a transaction involving a sale, purchase, reorganization, or transfer of any asset of MGM Resorts International and/or any individual MGM Resort or MGM Online Service.

4\. YOUR COMMUNICATION PREFERENCES

**A. Guestbooks**

By using our Guestbooks, you can view and update your contact information and choose which MGM Resorts and MGM Online Services you are most interested in hearing from. You can also select from among various communications preferences including direct mail, e-mail, telemarketing, and text messaging. To use our Guestbooks, please click [here](https://secure02.mgm-mirage.com/Guestbook/Guestbook.aspx?PID=205).

**B. How to Opt-Out**

If you wish to opt-out of receiving marketing solicitations from us, or do not want us to share your Personal Information for marketing purposes with our business partners or other third parties, or with any individual MGM Resort, or MGM Subsidiary please e-mail us: [optout@mgmresorts.com](mailto:optout@mgmresorts.com), call us: (866) 761-7111, or write to us:

MGM Resorts International  
Attn: OPT-OUT  
3549 Sammy Davis Jr. Drive  
Las Vegas, Nevada 89109

Although you may opt-out of the use and sharing of Personal Information for marketing purposes, we may still use and share information we collect for Non-Marketing Purposes.

For information on how to opt-out of some uses of information collected by third-party advertising companies at (or through) MGM Online Services, please click [here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).

**C. Telemarketing**

Even if you registered your telephone number on a do-not-call list, certain exemptions may allow us to contact you by telephone. However, to ensure your preferences are honored, we also maintain our own internal do-not-call list. If you would like to opt-out of receiving telemarketing sales calls from us add your telephone number to our internal do-not-call list, please click [here](http://www.mgmresorts.com/dnc/).

5\. YOUR CALIFORNIA PRIVACY RIGHTS

California law requires certain businesses to respond to requests from California residents asking about the disclosure of Personal Information to third parties for third party marketing purposes. Alternately, such businesses may adopt a policy of not disclosing Personal Information to third parties for marketing purposes if a California resident has opted-out of such information sharing.

We have an opt-out policy in place. If you wish to opt-out of our sharing your Personal Information with third parties for marketing purposes, please follow the “How to Opt-Out” instructions in Section 4(B), above.

6\. SECURITY

Information maintained in electronic form that is collected by MGM Resorts International and any individual MGM Resort is stored on systems protected by industry standard security measures. These security measures are intended to protect these systems from unauthorized access. No security system is impenetrable and these systems could become accessible in the event of a security breach. We have controls in place that are designed to detect potential data breaches, contain and minimize the loss of data, and conduct forensic investigations of a breach.

Our staff is required to take reasonable measures to ensure that unauthorized persons cannot view or access your Personal Information. Employees who violate our privacy policies are subject to disciplinary action, up to and including termination of employment.

We cannot enforce or control the security of the computers, electronic devices, or electronic communication method(s) you may use to send e-mails and submit information to us. You are responsible for the security of the computers, electronic devices, and electronic communication methods you use to communicate with us. We are not responsible for the disclosure or interception of information you send us before we receive it.

As a standard security practice, we take reasonable steps which are generally recognized in the industry to ensure that the communication methods used to support MGM Online Services do not permit connections or communication by methods that have known security weaknesses or vulnerabilities. As such, if you experience trouble using an MGM website, it may be an indication that you need to upgrade your software to a newer version that supports more secure communication methods.

In situations where your Personal Information is collected by third parties under contract with us for performance of their contractual duties and other purposes, we require such third parties to exercise reasonable care to protect that information and restrict the use of your Personal Information to the purposes for which it was provided.

7\. OTHER WEB SITES

We are not responsible for the information collection or privacy practices of other websites, including websites operated by our business partners or other third parties, including websites that might be co-branded with our name.

You should review and understand the privacy policies posted on any linked sites you visit before using those sites or providing any Personal Information through them.

8\. PERSONS UNDER AGES 13 AND 21

Certain of our areas and activities are intended for persons 21 or older. If you are under 21, you may not access or attempt to access any areas or participate in any activities that are restricted to persons 21 or older. We do not knowingly collect or allow the collection of Personal Information from persons under 13.

If you are the parent or guardian of a person under 13 and believe that the person has provided us with Personal Information, you may contact us at [privacy@mgmresorts.com](mailto:privacy@mgmresorts.com)and request that it be removed from our active marketing database.

9\. CHANGES TO THIS POLICY

We reserve the right to revise this Policy at any time without notice. When this Policy is revised in a material way, notice will be posted on MGM websites that we control along with the revised Policy.
